= kisskh.club =
Previously on Dating Alys Perez.
Alys
Zyril
Perez,
will you marry me?
I now pronounce you,
man and wife.
So, where are we going?
I just can't believe we're finally married!
You will get married.
And you'll do what I say!
If he doesn't marry you,
then you're not coming home!
I'll cut all your resources!
You will stay here until
that jerk marries you!
Stop it, Alys.
We both know how this is going to end.
One of us has to go.
You're married to him.
And we're having a child.
Can't you see how
crazy our situation is?
This baby will be labeled a bastard, Alys.
A bastard!
Fier, wait!
- Wait, let's talk—
- Ouch!
- Oh my god! Fier, are you okay?
Fier, how are you feeling?
Shut up, Alys!
Ouch!
- Do you want to go to the ER?
- Stop it, Alys!
- Alys, stop!
- Please.
- Fier!
- Where does it hurt?
- What happened?
I don't know.
She just started screaming.
Drake,
would you tell your wife
that I'm not here to be her best friend.
Stop trying to be my friend.
I don’t need one.
- Fier, let me —
- No need!
I can do this.
I don’t need your help.
Drake, I'm sorry, I didn't know
it would be bad for her.
I didn't know it would
be bad for the baby.
I’m so sorry.
It's not your fault.
Have you eaten?
What about Fier?
Okay.
I'll talk to her.
Please check on her.
Is she really that mad at me
that even when she’s struggling
she won't accept my help?
Was it a mistake to move here?
Maybe Tofer was right.
Living here has done
more harm than good.
Alys.
Uncle! Good evening.
What are you doing here?
Is Drake still not here?
He's upstairs, talking to Fier.
Oh, I see.
Uhm...
Uncle?
Is there something you’d like to say?
I really don't know what to say, Alys.
All I know is, I want you for Drake.
And I'm happy you're married.
But Fier,
she’s carrying my grandchild.
And I can't make her leave.
Uncle Steve.
It’s just hard to be
in the middle, Alys.
Alys, don't worry.
I just need to rest.
Excuse me.
All I want is for us to be civil.
The three of us.
We can do it, right?
I won’t abandon you, Fier.
And all you need to do is to cooperate.
Civil?
You think it's that easy?
You think just because I’m under
your roof, you can control me?
I'm not Alys.
I’m not someone you can order around.
You don't own me.
You can’t control me
whenever you want.
Well if that's the case,
it's probably better
if you don't stay here.
Let’s think of another way
to make this work.
If I had any other choice.
Well, you're right.
And you know that I love Alys.
And because I love her so much,
I'll do whatever it takes
to fix things between us.
So if you want to slap me,
go on.
I'll just stand here and take it.
But don’t get confused, Fier.
You can hurt me.
But you can never hurt Alys.
Drake!
She slapped him again.
Does it hurt a lot?
Liar.
I have a solution, Drake.
Alys,
please don't tell me
you're leaving again.
I'm not leaving.
You’ll still see me anyway.
It’s just that I won’t
be living here anymore.
So you are leaving?
Dummy!
I'm married to you!
How far do you think I'll go?
Even if you’re just an
inch away from me, I’ll miss you.
If I could just put you in my pocket,
I would’ve done it already.
You must have put a spell on me
so I'd go crazy without you.
Drake, my decision is final.
I'm leaving for now.
But don't worry,
I'm not running away from you.
It just hurts seeing Fier take her
anger out on you because of me.
I’ll always be one call away.
You're sure you won't
run away from me?
Never!
To the moon and back, remember?
Yeah.
To the moon and back.
Alys.
Hmm?
I love you.
I love you more.
I love you most.
Mom, Dad, I'm really sorry
about my decision with Drake.
It's done, dear.
You’re married now.
There's nothing we can do about it.
And I realized that you're at the
right age to decide for yourself.
What matter's most is that
you stand by your decision,
that you are ready for all
the consequences.
Okay, dear?
Thanks, Mom.
You know what Alys,
I truly wish you all the best.
More than anything,
your peace of mind.
Alys,
what if you just come home?
At least, you won't be alone.
You'd be with me, Dane and your mom.
No, I'm fine, Dad.
I want to learn how to live on my own.
And besides, I don't want to live under
your shadow for the rest of your lives.
And I know that
you guys mean well, but
I just really need this for myself.
Okay, dear.
I understand.
As long as you call us if
you ever need anything, alright?
Home is always waiting
in case you change your mind.
I know.
Anything you need,
we're always here, okay?
Okay, Dad.
Thanks, Mom.
Thanks, Dad.
Love you, bye.
Hello, husband.
Drake?
You okay?
Why are you so quiet?
I'm just worried about you, Alys.
Come on.
I'm fine!
We're fine.
Alys, tell me the truth.
How are you?
Honestly, a little tired.
But...
considering everything that's happened,
this is the least that I can do.
I want to be with you.
This is only temporary, Drake.
I just...
I don’t want to be the reason
Fier’s pregnancy becomes complicated.
This is all for the better.
Trust me, okay?
Alys?
I'm sorry you have
to go through all this.
Don't be sorry, Drake.
We decided this together.
So, we have to face this together.
Don't worry.
It'll only be for less than a year.
After Fier gives birth,
everything will be alright.
Okay?
I'm so lucky to have you, Alys.
- I love you.
Stop moving.
Bestie, it's already too thick!
How are we supposed to look good then?
I don’t —
It's done!
Stop complaining.
Fine.
I already put it on you,
and you didn’t even say thank you.
So...
- What?
- How long are you staying here?
I bet you'll be back
at Drake's in one week.
You're so mean to me.
But you know, Bestie?
Hmm?
I'm honestly impressed.
How do you handle this?
Honestly, I don’t even know
how I manage to do this.
I guess that's how it is
with your one true love.
I don't know what's with you, Bestie.
You’re being such a martyr.
Oh gosh!
Wait.
How is your shop doing, by the way?
Well, I haven't checked
in on it for a while.
Good thing I have staff I can trust.
Mhm.
You know, Bestie,
I really missed this.
Our sleepovers.
Our playful banters.
I wish we were back in high school.
Do you remember what our only
problem was back then?
Whether we should copy
each other’s answers.
You know what I never
understood back then?
Why did we even copy off each other
when we were both stupid?
I mean,
what kind of grades did we expect?
Team Stupid.
What I’m going to eat at the cafeteria?
What course I’m going to take in college?
Whether you’d graduate.
You’re being too much.
You’re really being too hard on me!
Bestie!
That was too much.
You know, I have a surprise for you.
What?
Close your eyes, first.
- What is it?
- Just close your eyes!
Aya, if that's a cockroach,
I'm telling you right now...
- What?
- Look.
- Stop! It's weird!
- Remember this, Bestie?
- Bestie!
- Stop that, Aya!
You're still a witch.
Stop it!
[In Japanese] Welcome!
Thank you!
Looks like we’re not busy today, huh?
Can’t I just miss you?
Miss me? Jeez...
Here. Go eat.
So...
How's your soap opera
of a life these days?
You know Tofer,
you're the biggest gossip ever.
But, the thing is...
I was just concerned for Fier because
she's having a hard time.
Wow, you’re more
concerned about Fier?
While you on the other hand,
have to suffer because of my cousin.
I've told you about this too many times.
You're just stubborn.
So, how is Tripp?
You know what,
you’re really good at
changing the subject.
Seriously, how is he?
Well, still nursing a broken heart.
Meanwhile, you're messed up dealing
with situation with Drake.
He's messed up too.
He hasn't really moved on from you.
You know, this isn't a joke, Tofer.
We're both fine.
I just talked to him!
You're just—
Gosh, fine!
Suit yourself if you
don’t want to believe me.
Hey!
You're spacing out again, Perez.
Looks like you’re still buffering.
Hey!
You're gross!
Thank you, Tofer.
Anytime, Perez.
Hey, Bestie!
What's up?
Where are you?
- Good morning, Ms. Aya.
- Good morning!
Good morning, Ms. Aya.
I'm with Tofer at Botejyu, why?
Oh, okay.
But I'm heading to Drake's office later.
You know, Bestie,
it's great that you're going out.
So you don’t have to think
about your problems all the time.
Yes, thank you, Bestie.
Okay.
See you soon.
Love you, bye!
Bye, bestie.
Eat up!
I am!
You too.
Eat!
Food trip!
Let's go!
With Botejyu!
Hello, husband!
I got you some food!
What are you doing here?
Can't I visit my husband?
What are you doing?
Just reading reports.
Okay.
How's Fier?
Why do you ask?
No reason.
I just want to know if she's okay.
I hope she and her baby are—
She's okay.
And she will be okay, Alys.
I missed you.
Come on.
You're always at my condo.
How can you miss me?
I will miss you every day.
All the time.
Every minute.
Every second.
Whatever you say, Drake Sebastian.
Okay.
Just keep doing whatever you're
doing and I'll just stay here.
Okay, wifey.
Okay, hubby.
Thank you, Drake.
Of course, I'm always
at your service, Alys.
I almost forgot, we didn't have dessert.
Do you want me to order
a strawberry shortcake?
And your car needs an oil change.
Let's have it done next week.
Drake...
What?
You don't have to
come with me every day.
What?
It's like you feel compelled
to be with me all the time
because we're married but
it's not the case.
Why?
Fier needs you.
Even if she doesn't need you,
your child will.
Alys, I'm doing everything I can.
Really?
Have you ever accompanied
her to a doctor's appointment?
Drake, I'm here with you.
I'm here to stay.
But you also need to
face your responsibilities.
But—
I'm a woman too.
And I know exactly what
Fier needs right now.
I'm always okay.
I promise.
Okay.
This is hard for me.
But I don’t want to make it harder for you.
I can bear it all,
as long as you don’t have to suffer.
I love you so much, Drake.
Drake.
Yes?
How's Alys?
Getting by.
Drake.
I know this is not my business.
But what are your plans?
You can't keep going on like this.
They're both getting hurt.
I know.
Fier is pregnant.
She can't keep getting
stressed out over Alys.
It's dangerous for the child.
And Alys...
Poor Alys.
Do you know how many times I
caught her crying while she was here?
I know she always says she's okay.
But she's breaking, Drake.
Soon, she'll be exhausted.
And look at yourself.
Aren't you getting tired of all this?
Fier...
I still won't marry you.
I know.
No.
You're not listening.
I'm married to Alys.
And we're having a kid.
But that’s as far as it goes.
Fier, please stop doing this.
Let's not make this any harder.
You knew from the very beginning,
it has always been Alys.
So, please.
Don't make things complicated.
Even if I beg over and over again,
that's fine with me, Fier.
Please.
Okay.
So now, what do you want?
I’ll get a house for you.
I'll make sure that you
will be well taken care of.
I'll go with you to all your check-ups.
And I'll give you everything you need.
I'll be beside you
whenever our child needs me.
Alys is right.
So Alys is the reason again?
Okay.
But for now,
can you leave me alone?
Leave!
Hello, Chance?
My decision is final.
Help me leave this country.
Yeah.
In a week.
- Shaira!
- Alys!
You poor thing!
We have to talk!
Hey! Shaira!
You don't have to harass Zy!
I'm not harassing her, you dummy!
I'm comforting her.
She deserves it.
And you!
If I hadn't called Tripp, I wouldn't
have known how wrecked your life is!
Hold on.
I was supposed to head out today.
No!
You need a real shake up!
This'll take a while, okay?
Sorry.
And then what?
And then one day,
while they were both single
at that time, they got drunk.
And then it just happened.
Oh my gosh, Drake!
He’s such a mess.
Now what?
So now, her father disowned her
all because he wants them to get married.
How can that happen
when we're married?
Exactly!
And Fier herself is somewhat
a complicated person.
So, just so I don't cause
any trouble and
to make sure Fier's pregnancy goes well,
I just decided to leave.
What?
She's making a point, right?
That's why I'm here
in this condo right now.
It's probably the hormones
that make her... difficult?
I'm not quite sure but,
I don't know.
I'm just trying to understand Fier.
Because I'm pretty sure what
she's going through isn't easy.
Hormones, my ass.
I have a cousin that's pregnant.
And she's nothing like that.
She's crazy as hell is what it is.
- Actually!
- Hey, don't get all worked up.
- What's so funny?
- Calm down.
This isn't a laughing matter, Alys.
Okay, maybe...
she is going through a lot.
I'll give her that.
But what you're going
through is no joke, Alys.
OMG!
I knew you were stupid
but not to this extent!
- Hey!
- My god, please!
You don't have to call her stupid!
That's what she is!
What's done is done.
It is what it is. It's over.
And also, did I mention?
Fier keeps slapping Drake!
- What?!
- I couldn't take it.
I can't take that.
I’d rather leave than
let that happen again.
That's it!
My patience has run out.
I'm gonna go and smack
some sense into that girl!
- Hey, calm down!
- Where are you going Shaira?
Hey, should we follow her?
Better not.
Let her be.
Are you good?
I can do this.
Hey.
Always remember...
I'm right here.
Of course.
I know.
Zy?
I want to ask you something.
Hmm?
How are you so calm about all this?
Why?
How should I be?
No.
What I mean is,
if it were someone else,
maybe everything at
Uncle Steve’s place is already broken.
Why am I like this?
I keep thinking
that I should be mad at Fier
but I try to understand her instead.
And she told me herself that
she never wanted to stay
there in the first place.
That she was a victim
of her dad's decision.
It hurts to be called a mistress.
It’s hard to be called a mistress.
To have your child be called a bastard.
I don't know.
Fier’s situation is
really difficult right now.
Well, you know,
if you feel bad for Fier,
I feel even worse for you.
Like you always say,
it's normal to cry.
But like I always say,
don't be hurt.
Jeez...
Our lives are so complicated.
Well...
Complications make the ending
much sweeter, don't you think?
Damn, you're good.
Damn right!
I really look up to you.
As you should.
So good.
Hey.
Where are you going?
I’ll follow Shaira.
I have a feeling I know where she went.
I'm coming too.
Let's go.
You know, sometimes I still wonder...
Why Drake?
Why not me? I'm more handsome.
Are you being serious?
Don’t argue with me.
That’s the only thing
that makes me feel better.
I look better than Drake.
Relax.
Just trying to make you laugh.
Tripp?
Hmm?
Thank you.
You never left me.
I hope you'll always stay.
I hope you never change.
Not yet.
I still can't.
What?
Nothing!
It's nothing!
Are you sure she's here?
Who the hell do you think you are?!
Are you some nepo baby or something?
Shame on you for causing this mess.
Told you.
- Shit!
- Shaira!
- You bitch!
And who are you?!
- Oh my god!
- That's enough, Ma'am.
Let go of me!
I'm not done with this bitch.
- Let me handle this.
- Who is this, anyway?
Who are you?
Why are you meddling with us?
I don't even know you.
Nosy bitch.
Excuse me?!
I'm the best friend of the guy
whose baby you're carrying.
And don't you dare
call me a bitch.
- Oh?
- Okay, okay.
So would you rather be
called a trashy bitch then?
Trashy bitch?
Shaira.
You came all the way
here just to yell at me.
Who in their right mind does that?
Crazy bitch!
I said don't call me a bitch, you bitch!
- Relax!
- Shaira, calm down.
Everything's fine, Shaira.
Please...
- Relax.
- My God.
What poison did she feed
Drake to get her pregnant?
Let alone even kiss her.
I can't stand the thought!
You dreadful woman.
Shaira, please! Stop it!
Actually...
You stop it!
Whoa.
I haven't a clue as to why
you're tolerating this bullshit!
Alys, you married Drake.
And in your pretty little mind,
you don't seem to understand.
Alys, wake up!
You're the wife!
Why did you have to leave?
Oh, fuck it.
Hey! I'm not done with
you yet, Ms. Homewrecker!
Shaira.
Miss Whoever-You-Are,
watch your fucking words!
You know nothing.
Oh... I know plenty!
And if Alys won't do anything about it,
I sure as hell will!
Whatever.
Believe what you want.
It's your life.
- Shaira.
- Wow!
- Walk off, girl!
- Okay.
- Walk off.
- Shaira, she's gone. Let's go.
Let's get out of here.
I'm not leaving.
I'm still waiting for Drake.
Has he gone insane?!
Jeez.
Oh my god!
Oh my god, he has gone insane!
That explains this!
What happened?
There you are!
Drake.
Did you hear all that?
She was yelling at me.
Where the hell did
you pick up that bitch?
What'll happen to my godchild?
The kid might grow up
with no manners.
Drake, come on.
Where are your standards?
I thought you were the
smartest person I know.
But apparently not.
If you wanted kids,
Alys is there anyway,
or any of your other exes.
Why does it have to be that woman?
Shaira, I'm really tired.
Tired?
You're tired, Drake?
The world doesn't revolve around you.
What about Alys?
Don't you think she's tired too?
I know Alys is a saint.
But it doesn't mean she agrees to all this!
Am I right, Alys?
Shaira.
Don't meddle.
Don't try to stop me!
Alys is my friend and
I can't stand what's happening!
It's foul on every single level.
Drake, you married her.
Now grow a pair and have
some goddamn responsibility.
What do you want me to do?
Be with her for Christ's sake!
Leave that woman to her family!
Your IQ is so high,
but your EQ is so low, Drake!
Do you really think their family
would cut off their only daughter?
My god, Drake, have I
become smarter than you?
Okay! Shaira...
Show's over. Let's go.
- I'll take you home.
- Gladly.
Drake, you're better than this.
We're going.
You two should talk.
Just...
Feel free to call me if you need me.
Alys.
Are you having a hard time?
It's the first time he asked me how I feel.
I just need to talk to Fier.
Okay?
Fier, please.
Spare us.
I want to be with Alys.
I'll still take care of you both.
Do you really love her that much?
Answer me!
Get up, Drake!
Do you think you can just
beg your way out of this?
Come on, Drake!
If you think it's hard for you,
its a thousand times worse for me!
Is this all my fault?!
Why do they keep
calling me a bitch?!
Did I steal you from Alys?
Did you have a girlfriend
when I was with you?
You didn't, right?
No woman ever wanted to be a mistress.
I don't want to be.
It was never my dream.
But what can I do?
You married Alys even
when you know I was here!
The one who’s going
to be your child’s mother.
Did you hear anything from me?
Nothing!
Because I fucking accepted it all!
Because I knew there was nothing.
It was Alys all along!
But Drake, consider how I feel.
I'm hurting too!
Fier.
Please.
I'll be a good father to our child.
But I really can't marry you.
So that's it?
Hmm?
Look.
I don't know why people
think you're so perfect.
You got me pregnant.
Yet somehow,
you want me gone from your life.
Yes, I threw myself at you.
But it takes two to fucking tango.
You wanted this, too.
I'm sorry, Fier.
What can your apology do now?
Is your apology going
to be the father of my child?
Of course not.
You know what, Drake?
You're so selfish!
Maybe it's my turn to
be a little bit selfish too.
I'll give you the freedom that you're
so fucking desperate to have.
You're free from all responsibility
towards me or your child.
But you should give up any
hope of seeing your child.
Do you hear me, Drake?
Not a chance!
From now on, you don’t
have a child anymore.
This child is mine,
and I’m their only parent.
Do you understand?!
Don't do this to me, please.
Don't look at me like that.
Isn't this what you wanted?
I'm giving it to you!
Don't expect me to
come on to your terms, Drake.
I wasn't born to be a saint.
I’m only human and I can be mean too.
This is the best I could give.
Fier!
Fier, wait!
Should I be happy now?
This is it.
She’s the one who decided
to walk out of our lives.
But why does it feel so wrong?
Why do I feel this way?
Drake?
It's okay to cry.
Are you alright?
I'm going to talk to Fier, okay?
I'm going to tell her that
it's okay for her to stay here.
Please don't be sad.
It hurts me to see you like this.
Is this what epic love feels like?
When someone you love is hurting,
it hurts you more.
It hurts three times as much.
Alys, why are you like this?
Like what?
Why did I fall
for a selfless girl like you?
I'm not like this to other people, Drake.
If it was for someone else,
I'd have put myself first.
Survival of the fittest, right?
But when it comes to you,
you're my priority.
I'm sure that you'd do
the same for me, right?
Drake?
Drake...
I love you, Alys.
I love you, my wife.
Don’t talk to Fier anymore.
But I want you guys to be okay.
Everything will be okay.
I know.
I know, baby.
I have already decided
to do things on my own.
I don’t want to see you regret because
you’re choosing me over your child.
I don't want you to regret this one day.
Fier, she's my life.
We've been through so much.
We’ve faced so many things together.
And I don’t want to lose Alys again.
I want to give her the best life.
A life without any hassle.
Without any more pain.
Because I love her so much.
I've been waiting so long for this chance.
How about us?
Fier, I keep telling you.
I'm going to take care of you both.
But I can't lie to you anymore.
Fier, have you ever
loved someone so much
that even when you forget about them
or push them away,
or even when you find someone else,
your heart still goes back to them.
Fier, please!
Please!
Spare us.
Do you love her that much?
Drake?
On the next episode of
Dating Alys Perez.
I don't know where Fier went.
She’s with Cristine.
I'm leaving Drake and everything.
When will you leave?
Please.
Don’t help Fier leave the country.
Will you be willing to let go of Drake?
Fier, please.
If you have a problem,
we can talk about it, please!
Just stop the car, Zy, please!